鲁德/兹维列夫 6-4 7-6⁷ 布勃利克/中岛布兰登 · 赛后场上采访
Fellas, a couple of great wins tonight.
伙计们 今晚两场漂亮的胜利
Casper, I want to start with you.
卡斯珀 先从你开始
Before your doubles match, Carlos won
你们双打之前 卡洛斯在这里
an absolutely epic match out here.
赢了一场绝对史诗级的比赛
Did that give you guys
那有没有给你们
a little extra confidence and freedom
多一点信心和放松
to come out here and play well?
让你们上场打出好表现？
Maybe.
也许吧
I mean, it was nerve-racking watching every
我是说 今天看每一场
match today.
都让人很紧张
So sometimes it's almost better to play
所以有时候上场打
than to watch from the sidelines.
几乎比在场边看要好
And luckily,
幸运的是
we avoided another match tiebreak now
我们这次避免了又一个抢十
and it was really fun.
真的很有趣
A great team effort to get two wins
团队一起拼下两场胜利
in this night's session was needed
今晚夜场正需要这个
after two tough losses, so really happy.
毕竟之前输了两场 真开心
And Sasha,
还有萨沙
all the guys here are singles players.
这里所有的球员都是单打选手
I think a lot of amateurs
我想很多业余爱好者
when they watch doubles, they say,
看双打的时候会说
why aren't you guys serving in volley?
你们为什么不发球上网？
Can you just respond to that?
你能回应一下这个吗？
Why don't you guys serve in volley?
你们为什么不发球上网？
Do you try to play like singles players
你试着像单打选手那样打吗
or do you try
还是你试着
to play like doubles players out here?
像双打选手那样打？
No, we try to play like singles players
不 我们像单打选手那样打
because if we would serve in volley,
因为如果我们发球上网，
we would lose very, very quickly.
我们会非常非常快就输掉。
So there's no point of doing that.
所以那样做没有意义。
I think we probably hit a little bit
我觉得我们的正手
of a bigger forehand
可能打得更重一点
than some doubles guys.
比一些双打选手
And doubles guys definitely volley better
而双打选手的截击肯定
than us.
比我们好
So, you know, it's a give and take,
所以 有得有失
but I'm very happy with the team effort.
但我对团队的表现非常满意
I think Carlos kicked it off with, you know,
我觉得卡洛斯开了个好头
probably the most important win
可能是这个周末
of the weekend.
最重要的一场胜利
And I'm very happy
我也很高兴
that we finished the day off with a win
我们也以一场胜利
as well.
结束了这一天